A Guide to the A. Linwood Holton Papers, 1968-1974
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A. Linwood Holton Papers, 1968-1974
The Library of Virginia
28253
26.65 cubic feet (71 boxes and 4 oversize boxes)
Holton, A. Linwood (Abner Linwood), 1923-
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Governor and Mrs. A. Linwood Holton through Alexander G. Gilliam, Jr., Special Assistant to Governor Holton, Richmond, Virginia, 15 April 1974.
Biographical Information
Abner Linwood Holton was born 21 September 1923 in Roanoke, Virginia, to Abner Linwood Holton and Edith Van Gorder Holton. He attended local schools, then received his B.A. from Washington and Lee University in 1944. Holton served in the United States Navy from 1943 to 1946. He then attended Harvard Law School, receiving his LL.B. in 1949. Admitted to the Virginia bar that same year, Holton commenced practicing in Roanoke. He became active in the Virginia Republican Party. He was the unsuccessful candidate for governor in 1965, then won election in 1969. Holton served as governor of Virginia from 1970 to 1974. After his term ended, he served as assistant secretary of state for congressional relations in 1974. Holton resigned that position and practiced law in Washington D.C. He married Virginia Harrison Rogers 10 January 1953, and had four children with her.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1968-1974, of A. Linwood Holton (1923- ), governor of Virginia from 1969 to 1974, consisting of acknowledgements, appointment books, articles, audiotapes, biographies, certificates, clippings, editorials, histories, interviews, invitations, letters, logs, motion pictures, notes, photographs, poems, programs, reports, reviews, schedules, speeches, summaries, videotapes, and other materials documenting Holton's election and governorship. Papers document Holton's election campaign; his inauguration; and his term as governor, including his meetings, conferences, and addresses to various business, civic, and political groups. Also included are commencement addresses to colleges and universities in Virginia. Papers also document state and national Republican Party activities, including President Richard Nixon's (1913-1994) 1972 reelection bid. There are audio- and videotapes of Holton's campaign, addresses, inaugurals, and interviews. Collection largely consists of personal files gleaned from the Governor's official papers at the time of their transfer to the Archives. Papers also cover Virginia First Lady Virginia "Jinx" Harrison Rogers Holton's activities, including meetings with various organizations and civic groups.
Contents List
- Super Schedule, 23 November 1969-12 January 1974. (Box 1-3)
  - Vol. 1, 23 November 1969-31 March 1970. (Box 1)
  - Vol. 1, 1 April 1970-30 June 1970. (Box 1)
  - Vol. 2, 1 July 1970 - 31 October 1970. (Box 1)
  - Vol. 2, 1 November 1970-28 February 1971. (Box 1)
  - Vol. 3, 1 March 1971-31 August 1971. (Box 1)
  - Vol. 3, 1 September 1971-26 December 1971. (Box 2)
  - Vol. 3, Trooper Compton's Schedule, 21 January 1970-1 November 1970. (Box 2)
  - Vol. 3, Trooper Compton's Schedule, 2 November 1970-5 March 1972. (Box 2)
  - Vol. 4, 2 January 1972-30 September 1972. (Box 2)
  - Vol. 5, 1 October 1972-31 December 1972. (Box 3)
  - Vol. 5, 1 January 1973-30 April 1973. (Box 3)
  - Vol. 6, 1 May 1973-3 August 1973. (Box 3)
  - Vol. 6, 4 August 1973-31 October 1973. (Box 3)
  - Vol. 7, 1 November 1973-12 January 1974. (Box 3)
- Personal Correspondence, 1970-1971. (Box 4-9)
  - Ab-As (Box 4)
  - Ba-Bi (Box 4)
  - Bl-Bo (Box 4)
  - Bo-By; Addenda, Ba-Br (Box 4)
  - Ca-Cu; Addenda, Ca-Cl (Box 4)
  - Da-Du; addenda, Da (Box 5)
  - Ea-Ev (Box 5)
  - Fa-Fu; Addenda, Fa-Fr (Box 5)
  - Ga-Gu; Addenda, Ga-Gu (Box 5)
  - Ha-Hu (Box 5)
  - Addenda, Ha-Hu (Box 6)
  - In-Iz (Box 6)
  - Je-Ju; Addenda, Ja-Jo (Box 6)
  - Ka-Kn; Addenda, Ka-Kr (Box 6)
  - La-Lu; Addenda, La-Ly (Box 6)
  - Ma-Mu (Box 6)
  - Addenda, Ma-Mu (Box 7)
  - Ne-Nu; Addenda, Na-Nu (Box 7)
  - Ol-Ow; Addenda, Ol-Oy (Box 7)
  - Pa-Po; Addenda, Pa-Pu (Box 7)
  - Qua (Box 7)
  - Ra-Ru (Box 7)
  - Addenda, Ra-Ru (Box 8)
  - Sa-Sy (Box 8)
  - Addenda, Sa-Sw (Box 8)
  - Ta-Tu; Addenda, Ta-Tu (Box 8)
  - Uh-Un (Box 8)
  - Va-Vo; Addenda, Va-Vi (Box 8)
  - Wa-Wr (Box 9)
  - Addenda, Wa-Wo (Box 9)
  - Yo-Zi; Addenda, Ye-Yo (Box 9)
  - Miscellany; Post-Election Congratulations (1969) (Box 9)
- Personal Correspondence, 1972-1974. (Box 10-14)
  - Ab-Ay; Addenda, Al-As (Box 10)
  - Ba-By (Box 10)
  - Addenda, Ba-By (Box 10)
  - Ca-Cu; Addenda, Ca-Cu (Box 10)
  - Da-Du; Addenda, Di-Du (Box 10)
  - Ea-Ev; Addenda, Ed-Ev (Box 11)
  - Fa-Fr; Addenda, Fa-Fr (Box 11)
  - Ga-Gy; Addenda, Ga-Gu (Box 11)
  - Ha-He (Box 11)
  - Hi-Hu (Box 11)
  - Addenda, Ha-Hy (Box 11)
  - Ia-Ig; Addenda, Ir (Box 12)
  - Je-Jo; Addenda, Ja-Jo (Box 12)
  - Ka-Kr; Addenda, Ke-Kr (Box 12)
  - La-Ly; Addenda, La-Ly (Box 12)
  - Mc (Box 12)
  - Ma-Mu (Box 12)
  - Addenda; Ma-Mu (Box 13)
  - Ne-No; Addenda, Ne-No (Box 13)
  - Ob-Ow; Addenda, Oc-Ou (Box 13)
  - Pa-Pu; Addenda, Ra-Ru (Box 13)
  - Qui (Box 13)
  - Ra-Ru; Addenda, Ra-Ru (Box 13)
  - Sa-Sm (Box 13)
  - Sm-Su (Box 14)
  - Addenda, Sc-Sw (Box 14)
  - Ta-Tw; Addenda, Ta-Ty (Box 14)
  - Us (Box 14)
  - Va-Vo; Addenda, Va-Vi (Box 14)
  - Wa-Wy; Addenda, Wa-Wr (Box 14)
  - Washington and Lee University (Box 14)
  - William & Mary LL.D. Degree (Box 14)
  - Yo-Zi; Addenda, Ye-Zu (Box 14)
- Gift Acknowledgements, 1970-1974. (Box 15-16)
  - 1970 (Box 15)
  - 1971 (Box 15)
  - 1972 (Box 16)
  - 1973 (Box 16)
  - January, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Gifts (cuff links) from Governor to Governor's Management Study, 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Gifts from Governor and Mrs. Holton, 1970 (Box 16)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968, 1970. (Box 17)
  - Condolences, Governor's father, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Certificate from William Calhoun, 1970 (Box 17)
- Memorabilia. (Box 17-18 and, Box 1-2)
  - The Holton (Poem) (Box 17)
  - Inscribed copy of Hello, Appalachia! (Box 17)
  - Log of telephone calls, etc., 23 August 1973-11 January 1974 (Box 17)
  - Log of telephone calls, 14 January-19 February 1974 (Box 17)
  - Summaries of General Assembly sessions, 1970-1973 (Box 17)
  - Addresses on openings of General Assembly sessions, 1970-1974 (Box 17)
  - Year-end reviews, 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - The Holton Years: A Summing Up, 1970-1974 (Box 17)
  - Inaugural address, 17 January 1970 (Box 17)
  - The Governor's Cabinet, October 1972 (Box 17)
  - State of the State: The New Virginia, September 1971 (Box 17)
  - Guest editorial by Governor, Law and Order, June 1972 (Box 17)
  - Holton interview, Presbyterian Survey, 6 September 1971 (Box 17)
  - Holton sketch, Current Biography, February 1971 (Box 17)
  - Linwood Holton: Election Balancing Act in Virginia, Ripon Forum, December 1969 (Box 17)
  - The Today Show, 19 March 1970, transcript of interview with Holton (Box 17)
  - Virginia Record, Inaugural Commemorative Edition, January 1970 (Box 17)
  - The Washington Monthly, April 1973 (Box 17)
  - Holton's notes re: appointment policies, etc., November-December 1969 (Box 17)
  - Holton's notes re: conversation with Ken Cole about Watergate, 1 November 1973 (Box 17)
  - Weekly summary of mail received, 20 December 1971-11 January 1974 (Box 17)
  - Holton's travel vouchers, 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - Reproductions of four sketches by Dennis Sayers (Box 18)
  - Certificates received, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Certificates, personal, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Souvenir photographs of Holton at Redskins games, Washington (Box 18)
  - Souvenir photo book of Holton visit to CONARC, 12 June 1972 (Box 18)
  - Souvenir photo book of 1970 Governor's Conference, Missouri (Box 18)
  - Souvenir photo book of Holton visit to Philip Morris, Inc., NY, 11 November 1971 (Box 18)
  - Inscribed photograph to Governor from John H. Chafee, Secretary of Navy, 23 March 1972 (Box 1)
  - Photograph of Governor and President Nixon, in dinner clothes, shaking hands (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Governor at Strategic Air Command Headquarters, Nebraska, Autumn 1973 (Box 1)
  - Booklet given to Governor by children at Tiny Angels Day Care Center, Church Hill, Richmond, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Photograph of portrait of Sir Thomas Gates, sent by Mr. J. T. Zuill, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Three photographs of Governor and President Nixon (one taken in Norfolk), 1973 (Box 1)
  - Certificate from Deputy Prime Minister of Greece, commemorating 150th anniversary of Greek War for Independence, December 1972 (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Jefferson's drawings of State Capitol, from Massachusetts Historical Society, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Cartoon of Governor from Highway Safety Division (Box 1)
  - Multilith sheets for reprints of articles concerning Governor Holton (Box 1)
  - Photograph album, opening of Bristol End Plant, Reynolds Metals, Bristol, Virginia, 28 January 1972 (Box 2)
  - Certificates of Appreciation, U. S. Treasury Savings Bond Drive, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
- Staige D. Blackford Working Files. (Box 19-20)
  - The Holton Years (Box 19)
  - Report on Virginia Radio and Television Stations and Newspapers, 15 June 1972 (Box 19)
  - Material sent to Mrs. John Frisbee for biography of Governor (Box 19)
  - Race Discrimination and Equal Employment (Box 19)
  - Busing (Box 19)
  - Governor's speeches on constitutional revision, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Clippings and speeches on the New South (Box 19)
  - Clippings on Governor's speeches (Box 20)
- Speeches, 1970-1974. (Box 20-26)
  - Inaugural address (typescript), 17 January 1970 (Box 20)
  - Inaugural address (printed), 17 January 1970 (Box 20)
  - Address to General Assembly (typescript), 20 January 1970 (Box 20)
  - Address to General Assembly (printed), 20 January 1970 (Box 20)
  - Agricultural Exposition Breakfast, 21 January 1970 (Box 20)
  - Governor's Day, 30 January 1970 (Box 20)
  - Introductory remarks, Sister City Dinner, 6 February 1970 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 13 February 1970 (Box 20)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 20 February 1970 (Box 20)
  - Garden Club of Virginia, 9 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Testimonial for Dr. Jerome H. Holland, 10 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Dairy Products Association Convention, 17 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Atlantic Companies' new branch, Roanoke, 18 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Public Relations Associaton Convention, 19 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Rotary International, 20 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Highway Safety Commission, 24 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Eastern Shore of Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 24 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Roanoke-Salem Chamber of Commerce, 25 March 1970 (Box 20)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner of Wayne County, North Carolina, 2 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Conference of Public Health Workers, 8 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Richmond-First Club Good Government Award, 9 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Regional Convention, Alpha Pi Alpha Fraternity, 10 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Annual Civic Luncheon, Norfolk, 10 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - W & L University, O. D. K. Chapter, 14 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Republican Leadership Conference, Republican Governor's Association, 17 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Introduction of Gov. Melvin H. Evans, Gov. of Virgin Islands, 20 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Division of Aeronautics and FAA Dinner, 23 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Rotary Convention, 26 April 1970 (Box 20)
  - Anheuser-Busch Groundbreaking29 April 1970 (Box 21)
  - Stratford Hall, 3 May 1970 (Box 21)
  - Agency head luncheon, 5 May 1970 (Box 21)
  - Commencement exercise, Virginia Union University, 24 May 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Chapter, American Society for Public Administration, 28 May 1970 (Box 21)
  - Altavista Plant Dedication, 28 May 1970 (Box 21)
  - Delmarva Advisory Council Luncheon, 2 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Old Dominion University Commencement, 7 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Hampton Roads Maritime Association, 50th Anniversary Dinner, 9 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture, 15 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Association of Broadcasters, 18 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - International Telephone and Telegraph Luncheon, 18 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia State Police Graduation Ceremonies, 19 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Southern Conference of the Council of State Governments, 25 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Republican Dinner, 26 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Mt. Zion Baptist Church, 28 June 1970 (Box 21)
  - Duffield Industrial Park, 6 July 1970 (Box 21)
  - AFL-CIO Convention, 17 July 1970 (Box 21)
  - Revenue Resources and Economic Study Commission, 4 August 1970 (Box 21)
  - News conference, 4 August 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Court Clerks Association, 14 August 1970 (Box 21)
  - New Communities Symposium, 20 August 1970 (Box 21)
  - Golden Anniversary of Vocational Rehabilitation, 25 August 1970 (Box 21)
  - Local Government Officials Conference, 31 August 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Department of Welfare and Institutions' Education Association's Fall Conference, 2 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - American Nuclear Society Dinner, 2 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - AAA Annual Safety Award Luncheon, 9 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award Dinner, 11 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Chief Officials, National Corporations, 12 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Republican Party of Texas, 15 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Bar Association of the City of Richmond, 17 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Annual Meeting, Virginia Society of CPA's, 17 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, 19-22 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia's Municipal League, 20 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Industrial Development Conference, 30 September 1970 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Industrial Development Conference, 1 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Industrial Development Conference, 6 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Industrial Development Conference, 9 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Industrial Development Conference, 13 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Industrial Development Conference, 14 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Report to Top Management, 15 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Annual Chicago Travel Luncheon, 16 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - American Jewish Committee, 19 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Navy Day Dinner, 27 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - League of Women Voters, 28 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia World Trade Conference, 28 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Education Association Convention, 28 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - 23rd Annual Highway Conference, 29 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Inauguration of Dr. Allix B. James, President Virginia Union University, 30 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Richmond Businessmen's Luncheon, 30 October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Keep America Beautiful Awards, 5 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Association of Professions, 7 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Association of Counties, 9 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - Inauguration of Dr. Warren W. Brandt, President Virginia Commonwealth University, 10 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - Veterans Day, 11 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - Report to Top Management, 12 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - Ninth Annual New York Travel Luncheon, 13 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - 34th Annual Convention, Virginia Hotel and Motel Association, 23 November 1970 (Box 22)
  - Lynchburg Peace Officer's Association, 1 December 1970 (Box 22)
  - Governor's Conference on the Family Food Dollar, 1 December 1970 (Box 22)
  - Salvation Army's Annual Civic Dinner, 2 December 1970 (Box 22)
  - 50th Anniverary Congregational Dinner, Church of the Epiphany, 8 December 1970 (Box 22)
  - Annual Citation Dinner, National Conference of Christians and Jews, 9 December 1970 (Box 22)
  - Governor's Address to the General Assembly (Printed), 6 January 1971 (Box 22)
  - Senate Finance Committee and House Appropriations Committee, 20 January 1971 (Box 22)
  - Chaplain Service of the Churches of Virginia, 21 January 1971 (Box 22)
  - Governor's Conference, 5 February 1971 (Box 22)
  - Committee on Public Works, U.S. Senate, 8 February 1971 (Box 22)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 17 February 1971 (Box 22)
  - Republican Party of Oklahoma, 27 February 1971 (Box 22)
  - National Service to Regional Councils, 8 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - National Conference on the Judiciary, 11 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - National Conference on the Judiciary, 14 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - Richmond Forum, 15 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - Flood Control and Internal Development, 15 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - J.C. Penney Management Seminar, 19 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Chapter, American Association of University Professors, 20 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - Harvard Club Dinner, 30 March 1971 (Box 22)
  - United Community Service, 1 April 1971 (Box 22)
  - Founder's Day, Roanoke College, 2 April 1971 (Box 22)
  - Savings Bond Meeting, 14 April 1971 (Box 22)
  - Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, 15 April 1971 (Box 22)
  - Luncheon, Frankfurt, Germany, 26 April 1971 (Box 22)
  - American Club, Antwerp, Belgium, 4 May 1971 (Box 22)
  - Richmond Federation of P.T.A.'s, 10 May 1971 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Jaycee State Convention, 21 May 1971 (Box 22)
  - Virginia State College Commencement, 23 May 1971 (Box 22)
  - Waynesboro-East Augusta Mental Health Associations, 25 May 1971 (Box 22)
  - V.P.I. Commencement Address, 5 June 1971 (Box 22)
  - Senate Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations, 8 June 1971 (Box 22)
  - Virginia State Bar Association, 11 June 1971 (Box 22)
  - 30th Anniversary, Washington National Airport, 16 June 1971 (Box 22)
  - Groundbreaking, Northern Virginia Subway System, 17 June 1971 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Bankers Association, 18 June 1971 (Box 22)
  - 23rd Annual Virginia Conference on Federal Taxation, 19 June 1971 (Box 22)
  - House Select Committee on Crime, 23 June 1971 (Box 23)
  - House Subcommittee on Oceanography, 23 June 1971 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Industrialization Group, 24 June 1971 (Box 23)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Thirteen Original States, 26 June 1971 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 28 June 1971 (Box 23)
  - American Judicature Society, 2 July 1971 (Box 23)
  - Republican Convention Speech, 20 August 1971 (Box 23)
  - Civic Clubs of Radford, Pulaski and Montgomery Counties, 23 August 1971 (Box 23)
  - AFL-CIO Annual Convention, 24 August 1971 (Box 23)
  - A.A.A. Highway Safety Awards Luncheon, 25 August 1971 (Box 23)
  - Governing Boards of Virginia Public Colleges and Universities, 1 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - Suburban Virginia Builders Association, 8 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - Presentation of Thomas Jefferson Award to Governor Godwin, 10 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - State-wide Conference, Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission, 17 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - Carillon Civic Association, 20 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - Friends of Ferrum College Banquet, 23 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - Roanoke Memorial Hospital, 24 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - Clergy Association of the Richmond Area, 27 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - National Business League, 29 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - Fifth District Dinner, 30 September 1971 (Box 23)
  - University of Virginia Graduate Business School Sponsors Dinner, 1 October 1971 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service, 4 October 1971 (Box 23)
  - Address to the General Assembly, 12 January 1972 (Box 24)
  - Keep Virginia Beautiful, Inc., 19 January 1972 (Box 24)
  - Reynolds Metal Plant Opening, 28 January 1972 (Box 24)
  - Inauguration of Dr. Thomas A. Graves, College of William and Mary, 5 February 1972 (Box 24)
  - Dedication of Rebuilt Georgia-Pacific Plywood Plant, 8 February 1972 (Box 24)
  - ABEX Dedication, 10 February 1972 (Box 24)
  - Savings Bond Luncheon, 17 February 1972 (Box 24)
  - Members of United for Public Schools, 29 February 1972 (Box 24)
  - Subcommittee of House Governmental Operations Committee, 2 March 1972 (Box 24)
  - General Assembly, 13 March 1972 (Box 24)
  - South Carolina Youth Council, 20 March 1972 (Box 24)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 22 March 1972 (Box 24)
  - Fund Raising Dinner for Botetourt County Courthouse, 24 March 1972 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute Centennial, 24 March 1972 (Box 24)
  - Virginia State Employee U.S. Savings Bond Campaign, 6 April 1972 (Box 24)
  - Student Cooperative Association, 8 April 1972 (Box 24)
  - Far East Trade Mission, Tokyo American Club, 19 April 1972 (Box 24)
  - Australian Trade Mission, American Club, Sydney, 26 April 1972 (Box 24)
  - State White House Conference on Aging, 5 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Student-Legislator Open Forum, 5 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Peninsula Council of Boy Scouts, 8 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Staffing Practices Conference, 8 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care, 15 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - State Agency Head Luncheon, 15 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Dedication of Standard Paper Manufacturing Company Recycling Plant, 18 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Commencement Exercises, Virginia Military Institute, 21 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Adult Graduation Classes, 23 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Northern Virginia Mental Health Association, 25 May 1972 (Box 24)
  - Republican Convention, 2 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - Southern Water Resources Conference, 8 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - Statewide Planning in Higher Education Conference, 8 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - Governor's Workshop on Youth Councils, 16 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - American Legion Boys' State of Virginia, 16 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - National Bureau of Standards, 16 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - American Society of Public Administration, 21 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - National Association of Counties, 26 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - Mount Rogers Craft Cabin, 29 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - National Parks Centennial Celebration and Blue Ridge Parkway Anniversary, 30 June 1972 (Box 24)
  - Fund-raising Dinner for Governor Arch Moore, 16 August 1972 (Box 24)
  - Title VIII Housing Seminar, 28 August 1972 (Box 24)
  - N.J. 15th District, Congressional Candidate Fuller H. Brooks, 30 August 1972 (Box 24)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, 4 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Natural Disaster Assistance Relief Plan, 4 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Drug Abuse Control Council, 4 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - National Conference of Governor's Highway Safety Representatives, 12 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Shipper's Dialogue South, 12 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Fund-raising Dinner for Kit Bond, 19 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Indian Festival, Jamestown, 23 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Dedication of Northern Virginia Training Center, 25 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - United Communities Fund Luncheon, 25 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Nixon Campaign, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 26 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Carroll County Republican State Central Committee Dinner, 29 September 1972 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Municipal League, 3 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Governor's Travel Reception, 4 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Report to Top Management, 5 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Rotary Club of Johnson City, Tennessee, 10 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - A.A.A. Clubs of Virginia, 12 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Holhouser for Governor Rally, 12 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Student Legal Forum, University of Virginia, 13 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Charlottesville-Albemarle Mental Health Association, 18 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Non-Metropolitan Growth Conference, 18 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Republican Fund Raising Rally, 20 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - The Churchmen's Club of Baltimore, 24 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - New Communities Workshop, 24 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Adams County Republican Committee Dinner/Rally, 25 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Highway Conference, 26 October 1972 (Box 24)
  - GOP Men's Night, 1 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Nixon Campaign, St. Louis, 2 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Dedication, Medical Center Buildings, University of Virginia, 10 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 13 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Region II Financial Responsibility Workshop, 14 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Southern States Cooperative Stockholders Meeting, 14 November 1972 (Box 25)